

# TONAVALENCIA

INTERACTIVE MEDIA DESIGN

tona.valencia@hotmail .com

(+57) 304 590 2690 http://tonavalencia.git hub.io

https://www.linkedin. () com/in/paula-valencia/

### **SKILLS**



Eclipse, SublimeText, Processing, InDesign, Premier.

### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish - English - Japanese

### **HOBBIES**

Music, Singing, Languages, Videogames.

### **SOCIAL SKILLS**

Excellent communication, Adaptability, interpersonal skills, teamwork, work under pressure, time management and leadership.

### **Personal Profile**

Hello, my name is Paula Valencia I'm an Interactive Media Designer from Colombia. I describe myself as a curious person, I love to learn new things and my passion is to create, music and other cultures. During my life I have developes skills that makes me able to work with User Experience, Graphic Design, Web Design, App Development, Video Editing and other aspects.

#### **Achivements**

7th place in contest of Japanese oratory 2010 1st Place Internal Archery Tournament 2014 4th place in contest of Japanese oratory 2015.

### **Education**

Icesi University. Cali, Colombia. 2013 - 2018 Current GPA 4.1/5.0. Nihon University. Mishima, Japan. Sept 2016 - Feb 2017. Tenrikyo Church Japanese Language Colombia 2015-2016. Hip Hop Group Icesi University, Colombia 2014-2015. Rock Group Icesi University (Singer) 2013-2015. Archery Team Icesi University 2013-2014. Coomeva High School, June 2013. Colombian-Japanese Association Cali, Colombia 2010-2012. Karate Do Goju Ryu Kenshokai, Colombia 2010-2011.

### **Work Experience**

#### IOL Colombia - July 2015 - July 2017

Responsible for Logo creating, Web Design, Web development, Brand Marketing.Community Manager - Social Managing.
Contacted and interacted with customers, provided customer support. Javier Valencia Garzón, (+52) 3006180477, javiervalenciag@hotmail.com

#### **Audiovisual Children Project 2014**

Responsible for logo and brochure diagramming and creation. Ph. Yamile Sandoval Romero, Santiago de Cali University, Colombia. yamilesandovalr@gmail.com

#### **Doctoral Thesis Cover Page September 2015**

Responsible for cover page diagramming and creation. Ph. Yamile Sandoval Romero, Huelva University, Spain.

#### **Doctoral Final Poster and Thesis Cover Page September 2016**

Responsible for poster and cover page diagramming and creation.

Ph. Damian Mendoza Zambrano, Huelva University, Sevilla University, Malaga University, Cádiz University, Spain. damiamendoza@gmail.com

#### FrutyJoy Logo and Flyer creation May 2017

Responsible for logo and Flyer creation. Amanda García, FrutyJoy Manager. frutyjoy@gmail.com https://www.facebook.com/frutyjoy/



.com (+57) 304 590 2690

(+57) 304 590 2690 http://tonavalencia.git hub.io

https://www.linkedin. () com/in/paula-valencia/

### **HABILIDADES**



Eclipse, SublimeText,
Processing, InDesign, Premier.

### **IDIOMAS**

Español - Inglés - Japonés

### **HOBBIES**

Música, Idiomas, Diseño y Videojuegos.

# HABILIDADES SOCIALES

Buena comunicación, Adaptabilidad , habilidades interpersonales, trabajo en equipo, trabajo bajo presión, manejo del tiempo y liderazgo.

#### **Perfil Personal**

Hola, mi nombre es Paula Valencia y soy una Diseñadora de Medios Interactivos de Colombia. Me describo a mi misma como una persona curiosa, me encanta aprender cosas nuevas y entre mis pasiones se encuentran el crear, la música y otras culturas. Durante mi vida he desarrollado habilidades que me permiten trabajar con User Experience, Diseño gráfico, Diseño Web, Desarrollo de Apps, Edición de Vídeo y otros aspectos.

### Logros

7 mo puesto en concurso de oratoria en Japonés 2010 1er Puesto en Torneo Interno de Tiro con Arco 2014 4to puesto en concurso de oratoria en Japonés 2015.

### Educación

Universidad Icesi. Cali, Colombia. 2013 - 2018 Promedio Actual 4.1/5.0. Nihon University. Mishima, Japan. Sept 2016 - Feb 2017. Iglesia Tenrikyo Jaonés Colombia 2015-2016.
Hip Hop Group Universidad Icesi, Colombia 2014-2015.
Grupo de Rock Universidad Icesi (Cantante) 2013-2015.
Grupo de Arquería Universidad Icesi 2013-2014.
Colegio Coomeva, Junio 2013.
Asociación Colombo-Japonesa 2010-2012.
Karate Do Goju Ryu Kenshokai, Colombia 2010-2011.

## **Experiencia Laboral**

#### IOL Colombia - Julio 2015 - Julio 2017

Responsable de creaión de Logo, Diseño Web, Maquetación web, Marketing de Marca. Community Manager - Manejo de Redes Sociales.

Contactar e interactuar con clientes y proveer soporte técnico.

Javier Valencia Garzón, (+52) 3006180477, javiervalenciag@hotmail.com

#### Diplomado Internacional de Contenido Audiovisual Infantil 2014

Responsable de creación de Logo, Diseño y diagramación de Brochure. Yamile Sandoval Romero, Santiago de Cali University, Colombia. ttyamilesandovalr@gmail.com

#### Portada de Tesis Doctoral Septiembre 2015

Diseño y diagramación de portada de Tesis doctoral. Ph. Yamile Sandoval Romero, Huelva University, Spain.

#### Portada y Poster de Tesis Doctoral Septiembre 2016

Diseño y diagramación de portada y poster de Tesis doctoral. Ph. Damian Mendoza Zambrano, Huelva University, Sevilla University, Malaga University, Cádiz University, Spain. damiamendoza@gmail.com

#### FrutyJoy Mayo 2017

Diseño de Logo, diagramación de piezas publicitarias y Volante. Amanda García, FrutyJoy Manager. frutyjoy@gmail.com https://www.facebook.com/frutyjoy/